http://www.cae-nyc.org/privacy

Donate
PrivacyCAE's COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACYONLINE PRIVACY POLICYThis site is owned and operated by The Center for Arts Education. Your privacy is important to us.We may gather certain types of information about our users. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.Information CAE gathers and tracksCAE gathers two types of information about users:•    Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, sign up or buy tickets for events, or make online donations.•    Information CAE gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to user needs. Under no circumstances does CAE divulge any information about an individual user to a third party unless required by law.Optional Voluntary InformationWe offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:1. Electronic newsletter policyCAE gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page.2. Online donations and ticket purchasingCAE offers online donation functionality to our users through our service provider Neon. Neon follows industry standard security practices and does not share your information with any third party unless required by law. CAE will never share any information about specific individuals gathered through the online donation function, online ticketing processing, or online event sign-up process with any third party unless required by law.ChildrenConsistent with the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.Usage trackingCAE tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. CAE sometimes tracks and catalogs the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.CookiesWe may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain personal information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. CAE uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above).You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you’ve set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site.Use of informationCAE uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to sign up for events. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (depending on the newsletter), and occasionally send out updates when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. CAE never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don’t track which terms a particular user enters.Sharing of the informationCAE uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and improve service. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.SecurityCAE’s webhosting provider squarespace.com uses secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. CAE’s internal networks also employ firewalls, anti-virus software, and other measures to protect data.Your consentBy using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by CAE. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.Ownership of Content.  All text, images, graphics, sounds and software code (“Content”) on the site are copyrighted property of CAE or others.  No part of the Content may be placed in the public domain.  You may not reproduce, redistribute, publish, change or otherwise use by electronic or any other means any of the Content without our prior written consent.  You shall use the site for permitted, lawful, personal uses only and not to increase traffic to other websites.  Any trademarks or service marks indicated on the site are the trademarks and/or service marks CAE or others.  They may not be used or displayed without the prior written consent of CAE or the appropriate right holder. Links to Third-Party Sites.  The site may contain links to sites owned and operated by other parties.  We are not responsible for and have no control over the privacy and data security practices or policies of those sites.  We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those sites prior to providing them with any Personal information.DONOR PRIVACY POLICYFor all donors, whether donations are made online, in person, or through the mail, CAE will not trade, share, or sell a donor’s personal information with anyone else, nor send donor mailings on behalf of other organizations.Opt-out policyWe give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:•    Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters.•    Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our usersAll donors, both offline and online, may opt-out of specific or all correspondence at any time by contacting CAE at info@caenyc.org, 212.971.3300, or 266 West 37 Street, 9th Floor, New York, NY, 10018.
Support The Center for Arts Education
Donate Now
© 1996-2020 The Center for Arts EducationPlease note our new address and phone number:299 Broadway, Suite 1300New York, NY 10007(212) 689-9500info@caenyc.org Subscribe for our latest news.
Email Address
Sign Up
Thank you!
Hours
Privacy
